// creating an array and passing the number, questions, options, and answers
let questions = [
  {
    numb: 1,
    question:
      "Which of the following CSS Property sets the pace of the transition to the next keyframe?",
    answer: "Animation-transition-function",
    options: [
      "Animation-pace-function",
      "Animation-transition-function",
      "Animation-timing-function",
      "None of the above",
    ],
  },
  {
    numb: 2,
    question: "Which of the following is a valid HTTP Method?",
    answer: "Get",
    options: ["Get", "Put", "Post", "All of the above"],
  },
  {
    numb: 3,
    question: "On which of the Architectural pattern AngularJS is based?",
    answer: "MVC Architecture Pattern",
    options: [
      "Observer Pattern",
      "Decorator Pattern",
      "MVC Architecture Pattern",
      "MVVM Architectural pattern",
    ],
  },
  {
    numb: 4,
    question: "What function is used to fire an event?",
    answer: "None of the above",
    options: ["Emit()", "fire()", "Calc()", "None of the above"],
  },
  {
    numb: 5,
    question:
      "Which of the following pattern is taken by the buffer.toString Method?",
    answer: "Encoding",
    options: ["Encoding", "Start", "End", "All of the above"],
  },
  {
    numb: 6,
    question: "All APIs of NodeJS are?",
    answer: "None of the above",
    options: [
      "Asynchronous",
      "Synchronous",
      "None of the above",
      "All of the above",
    ],
  },
  {
    numb: 7,
    question: "What is Express.js?",
    answer: "A Web server framework for Node.js",
    options: [
      "A database",
      "A frontend framework",
      "A Web server framework for Node.js",
      "An operating system",
    ],
  },
  {
    numb: 8,
    question: " The functionality of angular controllers in the application is",
    answer: "None of the above",
    options: [
      "Used for displaying the data",
      "Used for controlling the data",
      "None of the above",
      "All of the above",
    ],
  },
  {
    numb: 9,
    question: "Which node module is used to handle binary data?",
    answer: "Buffer",
    options: ["Binary", "Buffer", "Crypto", "Dgram"],
  },
  {
    numb: 10,
    question:
      "Which of the following is a popular front-end framework for building user interfaces in JavaScript?",
    answer: "Angular",
    options: ["Django", "Angular", "Flask", "Node.js"],
  },
  //
  {
    numb: 11,
    question: "What is callback?",
    answer: "None of the above",
    options: [
      "The callback is a technique in which a method calls back the caller method",
      "The callback is a asynchronous equivalent for a function",
      "None of the above",
      "All of the above",
    ],
  },
  {
    numb: 12,
    question: " The total $RootScope an AngularJS application can have is?",
    answer: "None of the above",
    options: ["0", "1", "2", "None of the above"],
  },
  {
    numb: 13,
    question:
      " Which of the following is a core component in an Angular application?",
    answer: "Directive",
    options: ["ViewController", "Directive", "Activity", "Observer"],
  },
  {
    numb: 14,
    question: "AngularJS is a ",
    answer: "Javascript framework",
    options: [
      "Java framework",
      "Javascript framework",
      "HTML Framework",
      "Sql framework",
    ],
  },
  {
    numb: 15,
    question: "Which of the following are the benefits of using modules?",
    answer: "All of the above",
    options: [
      "Provides a mean of dividing up tasks ",
      "Provides a mean of reusing program codes",
      "Provides a mean of testing individual parts of a program",
      "All of the above",
    ],
  },
];
